export let scquestions=[{"num":"1","question":"1. Pollination by birds is called:","ptn1":"a) autogamy","ptn2":"b) ornithophily","ptn3":"c) entomophily","ptn4":"d) anemophily","right":"b","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"2","question":"2. Bees must collect nectar from approximately how many flowers to make 1 pound of honeycomb?","ptn1":"a)10 thousand","ptn2":"b)2 million","ptn3":"c)20 million ","ptn4":"d)50 million ","right":"c","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"3","question":"3. The only species of cat that lives and hunts in groups is:","ptn1":"a) lion","ptn2":"b)leopard","ptn3":"c)jaguar","ptn4":"d)cougar","right":"a","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"4","question":"4. Which prefix is often used with scientific terms to indicate that something is the same, equal or constant?","ptn1":"a)iso","ptn2":"b)mega","ptn3":"c)meta","ptn4":"d)quasi","right":"a","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"5","question":"5. The study of phenomena at very low temperatures is called:","ptn1":"a)heat transfer","ptn2":"b)morphology","ptn3":"c)crystallography","ptn4":"d)cryogenics","right":"d","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"6","question":"6.The branch of medical science which is concerned with the study of disease as it affects a community of people is called: ","ptn1":"a)epidemiology","ptn2":"b)oncology","ptn3":"c)paleontogy","ptn4":"d)pathology","right":"a","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"7","question":"7. The study of how people use tools to perform work and how people physically relate to their working environment is called: ","ptn1":"a)engineering","ptn2":"b)ergonomics","ptn3":"c)agronomy","ptn4":"d)physiology","right":"b","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"8","question":"8. Superconductivity is a material property associated with:","ptn1":"a)cooling a substance without a phase change","ptn2":"b)frictionless liquid flow","ptn3":"c) a loss of thermal resistance","ptn4":"d) a loss of electrical resistance","right":"d","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"9","question":"9. Cystitis is the infection of which of the following?","ptn1":"a)liver","ptn2":"b)urinary bladder","ptn3":"c)pancreas","ptn4":"d)lung","right":"b","answered":"0","given":""},
{"num":"10","question":"10. Which of the following is primarily composed of calcium carbonate?","ptn1":"a)Fish scales","ptn2":"b)Shark teeth","ptn3":"c)Oyster Shells","ptn4":"d)Whale bones","right":"c","answered":"0","given":""}];
